datersearch.com 2015-03-17

# Datersearch - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Datersearch.com (‘Website’), owned, managed, and operated by Boss Marketing LLC (‘Company’ or ‘We’ or ‘Our’ or ‘Us’), a company registered in Delaware, is an online platform offering dating services to a mature audience. We give top priority to the online privacy of the users of this Website (‘You’ or ‘Your’). In pursuance thereof, this Privacy Policy (‘Policy’) will inform You about Our general practices pertaining to personal and non-personal information - collection, usage, protection and disclosure.

We reserve the right to update, change, and modify this Policy at any time without assigning any reason to anyone and in Our sole discretion. However, We may post any major changes and modifications to this Policy on the Website homepage demanding Your attention. All such modifications shall be posted on this page and shall be effective from the time of such posting. Your continued use of the Website signifies Your implied acceptance of such modified Policy. We, therefore, encourage You to visit this page often to remain updated on all such modifications

Last Updated on October 31, 2014

**Privacy of Children**

This Website is targeted exclusively towards users of or above 18 years of age. If You are under the age of 18 years, kindly cease all further usage of this Website. We do not intentionally ask for or collect any information from the minors. If We are made aware that We are in possession of any personally identifiable information about a minor, We shall take appropriate steps immediately towards purging such information from Our systems.

**Personal Information – Collection and Use**

During registration process, profile creating, and certain other processes, We collect some personal information from You, including without limitation, Your name, age, gender, email address, height, dependants (if any), body-type, religion, personal interests, education, occupation, etc. You may also post Your picture on Your profile page. The picture(s) and profile of the members are displayed for general viewing. Email address of the member is, however, not publicly displayed and is used exclusively for the purposes of inviting friends, adding friends, and sending notifications within a member’s personal network. The members interact among each other via the interactive feature on the Website without disclosing their email addresses.

Additionally, all the personal information so collected is used to:

  1. authenticate and send notifications to the members about the services offered, latest news, updates, events, contests, newsletters, etc. on the Website. However, You can always opt-out of the mailing list by managing Your account on the Website;
  2. enable other members to search and communicate with each other;
  3. provide You with personalized services; and
  4. troubleshoot.

We also collect email addresses of your friends to send invitation to join the Website in case You have used the automated invitation system offered on the Website.

In case You are interested in buying any product and/or service from this Website, if offered, We may collect Your financial information, like Your credit card details, in order to process Your order.

We do not sell, trade, rent out, or otherwise commercially exploit any of the personal information so collected.

We may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on the Website in collaboration with Our partners or a third party sponsor/promoter. In order to participate, You may be asked to provide some additional personal information, which may be shared with such sponsor/promoter.

**Non-Personal Information – Collection and Use**

We also collect some non-personal information while You browse different pages on this Website. Such information includes, without limitation, Your Internet Protocol (IP) address, IP address of Your Internet Service Provider (ISP), other demographic information, aggregate user data, browser type, operating system, etc. We use cookies to collect such information. Cookies are small text files placed on the hard disk of Your computer system by Our servers while You are browsing this Website. Our cookies are 100% safe and worm-free. Cookies are uniquely assigned to every user, and can only be read by a web-server in the domain that issued the cookie to such user. You can refuse to accept cookies by managing Your browser preferences. However, in order to enjoy the browsing experience of this Website, We strongly recommend You to accept Our cookies.

This information is used to:

  1. effectively manage the Website and improve the services offered through it;
  2. attract advertisers to the Website and deliver targeted advertisements to You, and ensuring that You are not offered same set of advertisements
  3. store Your preferences and record session information so that You don’t have to log in repeatedly; and
  4. customize newsletter, advertising, and webpage content based on browser type and user profile information.

In order to achieve the above-stated purposes, We reserve the right to allow Our advertisers to access the cookies deposited by Us on Your computer system. Except as provided herein, Your non-personal information so collected shall not be shared with any third party, without Your prior express consent. However, this stipulation does not apply to sharing the information with auditors, promoters, advertisers, partners, and other legal person under the appropriate burden of confidentiality.

**Security of Information**

We have deployed state-of-the-art security measures and technologies in order to safeguard Your information so collected. Additionally, several administrative checks are installed in order to prevent unauthorized access to Your information so collected. However, due to rapid technological advancements, We cannot undertake a foolproof guarantee about any unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors that may compromise the security of Your information at any time.

**External Links**

This Website may contain external third party website links either through advertisements or in members’ communications. All Your dealings with such third parties are subject to the privacy policy and other terms and conditions set forth by that website. We shall not be liable for any claim arising out of Your transactions with the third party, the links of which are accessible through this Website.

**Editing Personal Profile Information**

You can edit any personal information You want at anytime by logging in to Your account on the Website.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

No personal information shall be disclosed to anyone, except –

  * In response to legal processes, like subpoena, or to comply with the law; or
  * To enforce Our Terms of Use Agreement; or
  * To protect Our rights; or
  * Disclosure by the members on publicly or privately accessible online or offline forum, like blogs, social networking websites, message boards, forums, etc.;
  * To protect the safety of the members of public and users/members of this Website; or
  * To a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of the Website, or substantially all of its assets, to that successor in interest.

**Contact Us**

Still concerned about Your privacy, please feel free to drop in Your queries [here](mailto:support@star-help.com). Physical mailing address: 2915 Ogletown Road, #1792. Newark, DE 19713

To unsubscribe from our mailing list, simply visit our support site at: [star-help.com](http://star-help.com/). From this page you're able to one-click unsubscribe from all future mailings.
